truffleshuffle.co.uk 2018-12-27

# TruffleShuffle.co.uk

* The data controller for this website and its associated services is TruffleShuffle Retail Ltd

 **How is your information used here?**  
Your name, address and contact details are used in order to enable us to deliver orders to you. We sometimes need to send service messages by email, phone or WhatsApp such as order updates. If you have given us permission, we may also send you information about products, services and promotions, by email or post. We sometimes use your personal information to prevent and detect fraud. We will sometimes show you our adverts when you are on third party websites so you can keep informed about new products which may be of interest to you. From time to time we invite selected customers to partake in online surveys where we collect information about your shopping and browsing experiences with us, in order to improve our service to you.  
Your date of birth may be used in order to prevent and detect fraud, and also to calculate eligibility for our “Buy Now, Pay Later” payment option.  
Your gender information may be used to direct you to the most appropriate parts of our website to enhance your shopping experience.  
We use your payment information to take payment, give refunds and prevent fraud. We cannot process your orders and fulfil our part of our contract with you without using this information.  
We use your contact history to ensure that we are able to give you the best possible customer service. We may sometimes use your contact history to train and inform our staff so that we can continue to provide you with our best in class customer service.  
We use the information we have stored about your purchase history and saved items in order to help you buy the products you are most interested in; to aid in our customer service commitment to you; and to ensure we know about the products you like so we can make more informed decisions about new product lines to develop in the future.  
We use information about the device you are using (phone, tablet, desktop computer etc) in order to ensure our website is best designed to work on your device and therefore offer you our best possible shopping experience.  
We use information about any social media accounts you have linked to your TruffleShuffle account in order to enable you to login to our website in the most convenient way possible to you. We may also use this information in order to provide product recommendations to you, both on our website and on third party websites.  
We use information about your responses to surveys and competitions in order to offer you the best possible shopping experience and ensure that you are able to participate fairly in any competition or promotion you have entered on our website or social media channels.

 **Sharing your information**  
We have not, do not and will not sell any of your personal data to any third party. We do however share data with third party service providers in order to enhance or protect your shopping experience. We would share that with the following companies in the following ways:  
Payment providers and delivery providers – without sharing your information with our trusted and accredited partners (Royal Mail, UPS, PayPal, Klarna, HSBC), we would not be able to process or deliver any orders you place with us.  
Accredited service providers – we may from time to time share information with marketing agencies and advertisers in order to deliver our marketing messages to you. Any exchange of data is performed under extreme caution and we have service agreements in place with any third party data handler to ensure your data is safe.  
Fraud, legal and credit partners – from time to time, we may need to share data with agencies in order to attempt to prevent fraud from happening against you or us.  
We may share anonymised information about your website browsing history in order to enhance your shopping experience and offer you the most relevant selection of products.

 **Marketing messages**  
If you have opted in to receive our marketing messages or product update alerts, we'll send you these messages by email, text, Facebook/Twitter/Instagram/WhatsApp. These messages are designed to keep you informed of new products we're offering, and any promotions, discounts and events we may be running which could improve your shopping experience with us.  
To stop receiving marketing messages from us at any time:  
Update your preferences in your account settings  
Click on the “unsubscribe” link in any marketing email received from us  
Contact our Customer Service team at any time and request to be unsubscribed.  
We will ensure that by requesting this change, we will ensure you no longer receive marketing messages from us.  
Please note that an unsubscribe request from marketing emails will not exclude you from receiving messages about any order you have placed with us; any product update emails you have signed up for; any customer service communications.

 **Keeping your information**  
We will hold on to your information for as long as you have an account with us, or as long as is needed to be able to provide our service or support to you.  
If absolutely necessary, we may hold some of your information even after your account has been closed, in order to comply with regulation, help with potential disputes, prevent fraud or to enforce our terms and conditions.

 **Your rights**  
You have the following rights relating to your personal information:

\- To be informed about how your personal information is being used  
\- To access the personal information we hold about you  
\- To request the correction of inaccurate personal information we hold about you (although you can probably do most of this through My Account  
\- To request that we delete your data, or stop processing it or collecting it, in some circumstances  
\- To stop direct marketing messages, which you can do through your account, and to withdraw consent for other consent-based processing at any time  
\- To request that we transfer t elements of your data either to you or another service provider  
\- To complain to the data protection regulator

If you have any questions about your privacy and associated rights, please contact us [here.](https://www.truffleshuffle.co.uk/contact_us)

TruffleShuffle.com, Third Way, Bristol, BS11 9HL, UK
